juniata.edu 2013-05-22

# Juniata College - Web Privacy Policy

### Juniata Web Privacy Policy

#### 9/15/10

Juniata is fully committed to providing an informative, accessible, and entertaining website for its visitors. We enjoy interacting with our audience and providing our users with appropriate and useful information. Visitors to any Juniata Webpage have an opportunity to contact us via e-mail with inquiries.

Juniata respects your privacy and will protect the information you share with us through any means of communication. This statement explains how Juniata collects, safeguards and may use the information you entrust to the college via the Juniata College World Wide website.

There are cases where Juniata College websites may request/or provide personal information such as userID, password, name, or address. To provide for your privacy in these instances, Juniata provides a secure server that transmits and receives scrambled data, which is decoded on the server side. This technology protects your information from being viewed by an outside user.

The collected information is used for internal college purposes and may be used to improve the content of the College's overall website. It will not be shared with other organizations to help them contact visitors. However, Juniata reserves the right to use the information to contact visitors for marketing purposes.

While Juniata strives to protect its users' personal information and privacy, it cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Juniata's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation.

#### Outside links

Juniata's Web content may link to content located on Internet servers not owned or affiliated with Juniata. These third party websites are neither monitored nor controlled by Juniata. As a result, this policy does not extend to those sites.

#### Server logs

Juniata's Web hosts collect and store information sent by your Web browser. This information includes:

  * the Internet Protocol (IP) address associated with the device in use, such as a personal computer, hand-held device or the firewall or proxy server of the user's network
  * the date and time the Web browser made the request
  * the address (URL) of the page or file requested
  * the address (URL) of the "referring page," the page the browser loaded immediately before the request
  * "user agent" information, which usually includes information about the browser software and operating system the computer or device is currently running
  * general technical data about Juniata's server health and activity at the time of the request

This information does not reveal personally identifiable information but allows us to analyze trends in how college systems are being used. This information, including reports generated from the information, is stored indefinitely. Reports may occasionally be shared with third party vendors for further analysis. By having this information available, Juniata is able to improve the performance and user experience of our website.

Juniata reserves the right at its discretion to make changes to this policy at any time. You may check this page periodically for updates.
